<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pat Sellers&#39; site</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Pat Sellers&#39; site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Sellers</title>
      <link>/2018-01-18-cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018-01-18-cv/</guid>
      <description>pasellers11@gmail.com
Davidson, NC
https://www.linkedin.com/in/patrickjsellers/
704-284-3503
EXECUTIVE PROFILESenior innovation and analytics leader. Experienced and creative leader in higher education, inspiring and implementing data driven decision-making and change across all parts of an organization. Creative use of data and technology to advance organizational goals. Deep expertise in quantitative and qualitative research and assessment. Demonstrated success in building, leading, and teaching research teams, and communicating research results to mobilize coalitions of diverse constituencies for change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test1a</title>
      <link>/posts/test1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/test1/</guid>
      <description>I hope that this test works.
summary(cars)## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.:19.0 3rd Qu.: 56.00 ## Max. :25.0 Max. :120.00plot(cars$speed,cars$dist)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Patrick Sellers</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a political science professor at Davidson College. My current teaching and research interests focus on data and visualizations in politics and broader society. Previously, I have held administrative roles at Davidson, most recently Vice President for Strategic Partnerships. In this administrative work, I helped lead Davidson&amp;rsquo;s partnership with edX and worked with campus constituencies to expand the use of data analytics in decision making. I also led Davidson&amp;rsquo;s 10th-year reaffirmation of SACSCOC reaccreditation in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Sellers</title>
      <link>/vitae/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/vitae/</guid>
      <description>a;sldkjf
I am a political science professor at Davidson College. My current teaching and research interests focus on data and visualizations in politics and broader society. Previously, I held administrative roles at Davidson, most recently Vice President for Strategic Partnerships. In this administrative work, I helped lead Davidson’s partnership with edX and worked with campus constituencies to expand the use of data analytics in decision making. I also led Davidson’s 10th-year reaffirmation of SACSCOC reaccreditation in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Sellers</title>
      <link>/vitae/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/vitae/</guid>
      <description>Email: pasellers11@gmail.com
LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/patrickjsellers/
Davidson, NC
704-284-3503
I am a political science professor at Davidson College. My current teaching and research interests focus on data and visualizations in politics and broader society. Previously, I held administrative roles at Davidson, most recently Vice President for Strategic Partnerships. In this administrative work, I helped lead Davidson&amp;rsquo;s partnership with edX and worked with campus constituencies to expand the use of data analytics in decision making.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/cis230/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cis230/</guid>
      <description>Sellers, PatSellers, Pat273242018-01-23T23:15:00Z2018-01-23T23:15:00Z416338889Davidson College197671045515.00falsefalsefalsefalseEN-USX-NONEX-NONE/* Style Definitions */table.MsoNormalTable{mso-style-name:&#34;Table Normal&#34;;mso-tstyle-rowband-size:0;mso-tstyle-colband-size:0;mso-style-noshow:yes;mso-style-priority:99;mso-style-parent:&#34;&#34;;mso-padding-alt:0in 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cv/</guid>
      <description>cv* {margin:0; padding:0; text-indent:0; }h1 { color: black; font-family:Calibri, sans-serif; font-style: normal; font-weight: bold; text-decoration: none; font-size: 12pt; }.a, a { color: #00F; font-family:Calibri, sans-serif; font-style: normal; font-weight: normal; text-decoration: underline; font-size: 12pt; }.p, p { color: black; font-family:Calibri, sans-serif; font-style: normal; font-weight: normal; text-decoration: none; font-size: 12pt; margin:0pt; }.s1 { color: #00F; font-family:Calibri, sans-serif; font-style: normal; font-weight: normal; text-decoration: none; font-size: 12pt; }.s2 { color: black; font-family:Calibri, sans-serif; font-style: normal; font-weight: bold; text-decoration: underline; font-size: 12pt; }.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>